{"filename": "Jack_Shephard", "chunks": [{"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["traveled", "to", "Sydney", "to", "find", "his", "father", "doctor", "Christian"], "start_time": 36370, "end_time": 39580, "start_index": 71, "end_index": 80}, "right": {"tokens": ["Early", "in", "his", "medical", "career", "he", "operates", "on", "a", "car", "crash", "victim"], "start_time": 41180, "end_time": 45040, "start_index": 81, "end_index": 93}, "puncted_text": "traveled to <GPE>Sydney</GPE> to find his father, Dr. <PERSON>Christian Shephard</PERSON>. Early in his medical career, he operates on a car crash victim", "segmented_puncted_text": "|traveled to <GPE>Sydney</GPE> to find his father, Dr. <PERSON>Christian Shephard</PERSON>.|Early in his medical career, he operates on a car crash victim", "global_chunk_number": 0, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["traveled", "to", "Sydney", "to", "find", "his", "father", "doctor", "Christian"], "start_time": 36370, "end_time": 39580, "start_index": 71, "end_index": 80}, "mid": {"tokens": ["Early", "in", "his", "medical", "career", "he", "operates", "on", "a", "car", "crash", "victim", "named", "Sarah", "whose", "spine", "was", "damaged", "in", "the", "accident", "He", "is", "convinced", "that", "surgery", "will", "not", "alleviate", "her", "paralysis", "and", "he", "is", "characteristically", "cold", "and", "direct", "with", "her", "about", "her", "chances", "The", "night", "before", "the", "operation"], "start_time": 41180, "end_time": 59900, "start_index": 81, "end_index": 129}, "right": {"tokens": ["works", "out", "by", "running", "the", "steps", "of", "a", "stadium", "and", "meets", "a", "man", "named", "Desmond"], "start_time": 60460, "end_time": 64880, "start_index": 130, "end_index": 145}, "puncted_text": "traveled to <GPE>Sydney</GPE> to find his father, Dr. <PERSON>Christian Shephard</PERSON>. Early in his medical career, he operates on a car crash victim named <PERSON>Sarah</PERSON>, whose spine was damaged in the accident. He is convinced that surgery will not alleviate her paralysis, and he is characteristically cold and direct with her about her chances. <TIME>The night</TIME> before the operation, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> works out by running the steps of a stadium and meets a man named <PERSON>Desmond</PERSON>,", "segmented_puncted_text": "traveled to <GPE>Sydney</GPE> to find his father, Dr. <PERSON>Christian Shephard</PERSON>.|Early in his medical career, he operates on a car crash victim named <PERSON>Sarah</PERSON>, whose spine was damaged in the accident. He is convinced that surgery will not alleviate her paralysis, and he is characteristically cold and direct with her about her chances. <TIME>The night</TIME> before the operation, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON>|works out by running the steps of a stadium and meets a man named <PERSON>Desmond</PERSON>,", "global_chunk_number": 1, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["and", "direct", "with", "her", "about", "her", "chances", "The", "night", "before", "the", "operation"], "start_time": 55350, "end_time": 59900, "start_index": 117, "end_index": 129}, "mid": {"tokens": ["works", "out", "by", "running", "the", "steps", "of", "a", "stadium", "and", "meets", "a", "man", "named", "Desmond", "who", "is", "training", "for", "a", "race", "around", "the", "world", "The", "two", "have", "a", "brief", "but", "meaningful", "conversation"], "start_time": 60460, "end_time": 70550, "start_index": 130, "end_index": 162}, "right": {"tokens": ["apprehension"], "start_time": 84120, "end_time": 85850, "start_index": 203, "end_index": 204}, "puncted_text": "and direct with her about her chances. <TIME>The night</TIME> before the operation, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> works out by running the steps of a stadium and meets a man named <PERSON>Desmond</PERSON>, who is training for a race around the world. The <CARDINAL>two</CARDINAL> have a brief but meaningful conversation. After the operation <DATE>the next day</DATE>, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> is convinced that it was a failure, but he and <PERSON>Sarah</PERSON> are startled to find that she can \" miraculously \" move her toes and has regained feeling in her legs. They eventually marry, despite Jack's apprehension", "segmented_puncted_text": "and direct with her about her chances. <TIME>The night</TIME> before the operation, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON>|works out by running the steps of a stadium and meets a man named <PERSON>Desmond</PERSON>, who is training for a race around the world. The <CARDINAL>two</CARDINAL> have a brief but meaningful conversation. After the operation <DATE>the next day</DATE>, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> is convinced that it was a failure, but he and <PERSON>Sarah</PERSON> are startled to find that she can \" miraculously \" move her toes and has regained feeling in her legs. They eventually marry, despite Jack's|apprehension", "global_chunk_number": 2, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["apprehension", "in", "the", "days", "preceding", "the", "ceremony", "Their", "marriage", "is", "soon", "strained", "under", "the", "pressure", "of", "his", "work", "and", "Sarah's", "different", "work", "schedule", "which", "causes", "them", "to", "see", "little", "of", "each", "other", "Some", "time", "later", "Jack", "and", "his", "father", "are", "working"], "start_time": 84120, "end_time": 99880, "start_index": 203, "end_index": 244}, "right": {"tokens": ["tumor", "patient", "named", "Angelo"], "start_time": 100120, "end_time": 101910, "start_index": 246, "end_index": 250}, "puncted_text": "apprehension in <DATE>the days</DATE> preceding the ceremony. Their marriage is soon strained under the pressure of his work and Sarah's different work schedule, which causes them to see little of each other. Some time later, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> and his father are working on a tumor patient named <PERSON>Angelo</PERSON>.", "segmented_puncted_text": "|apprehension in <DATE>the days</DATE> preceding the ceremony. Their marriage is soon strained under the pressure of his work and Sarah's different work schedule, which causes them to see little of each other. Some time later, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> and his father are working on a|tumor patient named <PERSON>Angelo</PERSON>.", "global_chunk_number": 3, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["little", "of", "each", "other", "Some", "time", "later", "Jack", "and", "his", "father", "are", "working"], "start_time": 95150, "end_time": 99880, "start_index": 231, "end_index": 244}, "mid": {"tokens": ["tumor", "patient", "named", "Angelo", "Angelo's", "daughter", "Gabriela", "is", "his", "translator", "Jack", "and", "his", "father", "think", "that", "the", "operation", "will", "not", "work", "like", "his", "miracle", "operation", "on", "Sarah"], "start_time": 100120, "end_time": 115820, "start_index": 246, "end_index": 273}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "little of each other. Some time later, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> and his father are working on a tumor patient named <PERSON>Angelo</PERSON>. Angelo's daughter <PERSON>Gabriela</PERSON> is his translator. <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> and his father think that the operation will not work like his miracle operation on <PERSON>Sarah</PERSON>.", "segmented_puncted_text": "little of each other. Some time later, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> and his father are working on a|tumor patient named <PERSON>Angelo</PERSON>. Angelo's daughter <PERSON>Gabriela</PERSON> is his translator. <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> and his father think that the operation will not work like his miracle operation on <PERSON>Sarah</PERSON>. |", "global_chunk_number": 4, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["being", "You", "will", "always", "need", "something", "to", "fix", "Jack"], "start_time": 156340, "end_time": 160780, "start_index": 385, "end_index": 394}, "right": {"tokens": ["being", "a", "workaholic", "feels", "he", "contributed", "to", "the", "failure", "of", "the", "marriage"], "start_time": 160810, "end_time": 164720, "start_index": 394, "end_index": 406}, "puncted_text": "being, \" You will always need something to fix. \" <PERSON>Jack</PERSON>, being a workaholic, feels he contributed to the failure of the marriage.", "segmented_puncted_text": "|being, \" You will always need something to fix. \" <PERSON>Jack</PERSON>,|being a workaholic, feels he contributed to the failure of the marriage.", "global_chunk_number": 5, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["being", "You", "will", "always", "need", "something", "to", "fix", "Jack"], "start_time": 156340, "end_time": 160780, "start_index": 385, "end_index": 394}, "mid": {"tokens": ["being", "a", "workaholic", "feels", "he", "contributed", "to", "the", "failure", "of", "the", "marriage", "His", "father", "Christian", "operates", "on", "a", "woman", "while", "under", "the", "influence", "of", "alcohol", "when", "a", "nurse", "tells", "Jack", "about", "this", "he", "relieves", "his", "father", "and", "takes", "over", "the", "surgery", "He", "is", "unable", "to", "repair", "the", "damage", "however", "and", "the", "woman", "dies", "Christian"], "start_time": 160810, "end_time": 180840, "start_index": 394, "end_index": 448}, "right": {"tokens": ["pressures", "Jack", "to", "sign", "a", "report", "saying", "the", "woman", "was", "beyond", "medical", "assistance"], "start_time": 180840, "end_time": 185290, "start_index": 448, "end_index": 461}, "puncted_text": "being, \" You will always need something to fix. \" <PERSON>Jack</PERSON>, being a workaholic, feels he contributed to the failure of the marriage. His father, <PERSON>Christian</PERSON>, operates on a woman while under the influence of alcohol; when a nurse tells <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> about this he relieves his father and takes over the surgery. He is unable to repair the damage, however, and the woman dies. <PERSON>Christian</PERSON> pressures <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> to sign a report saying the woman was beyond medical assistance,", "segmented_puncted_text": "being, \" You will always need something to fix. \" <PERSON>Jack</PERSON>,|being a workaholic, feels he contributed to the failure of the marriage. His father, <PERSON>Christian</PERSON>, operates on a woman while under the influence of alcohol; when a nurse tells <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> about this he relieves his father and takes over the surgery. He is unable to repair the damage, however, and the woman dies. <PERSON>Christian</PERSON>|pressures <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> to sign a report saying the woman was beyond medical assistance,", "global_chunk_number": 6, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["is", "unable", "to", "repair", "the", "damage", "however", "and", "the", "woman", "dies", "Christian"], "start_time": 176230, "end_time": 180840, "start_index": 436, "end_index": 448}, "mid": {"tokens": ["pressures", "Jack", "to", "sign", "a", "report", "saying", "the", "woman", "was", "beyond", "medical", "assistance", "but", "during", "the", "inquiry", "Jack", "discovers", "that", "the", "woman", "was", "pregnant", "and", "reveals", "that", "his", "father", "had", "caused", "fatal", "damage", "by", "severing", "her", "hepatic", "artery", "His", "father", "flees", "with", "his", "medical", "career", "shattered", "eventually", "ending"], "start_time": 180840, "end_time": 199940, "start_index": 448, "end_index": 496}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "is unable to repair the damage, however, and the woman dies. <PERSON>Christian</PERSON> pressures <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> to sign a report saying the woman was beyond medical assistance, but during the inquiry <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> discovers that the woman was pregnant and reveals that his father had caused fatal damage by severing her hepatic artery. His father flees with his medical career shattered, eventually ending", "segmented_puncted_text": "is unable to repair the damage, however, and the woman dies. <PERSON>Christian</PERSON>|pressures <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> to sign a report saying the woman was beyond medical assistance, but during the inquiry <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> discovers that the woman was pregnant and reveals that his father had caused fatal damage by severing her hepatic artery. His father flees with his medical career shattered, eventually ending |", "global_chunk_number": 7, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["flees", "with", "his", "medical", "career", "shattered", "eventually", "ending"], "start_time": 195940, "end_time": 199940, "start_index": 488, "end_index": 496}, "mid": {"tokens": ["Jack", "leaves", "the", "United", "States", "he", "knows"], "start_time": 217680, "end_time": 220220, "start_index": 547, "end_index": 554}, "right": {"tokens": ["Eventually", "he", "finds", "him", "in", "a", "Sydney", "morgue", "Jack", "has"], "start_time": 222410, "end_time": 226100, "start_index": 560, "end_index": 570}, "puncted_text": "flees with his medical career shattered, eventually ending up in <GPE>Sydney</GPE>. While there, <PERSON>Christian</PERSON> encounters <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> in a bar and tells him that he wanted to apologize and tell his son that he did the right thing, but is too weak to call him. <PERSON>Christian Shephard</PERSON> later dies of a massive heart attack brought on by alcohol poisoning. When <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> leaves <GPE>the United States</GPE>, he knows only that his father is missing. Eventually he finds him in a <GPE>Sydney</GPE> morgue. <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> has", "segmented_puncted_text": "flees with his medical career shattered, eventually ending up in <GPE>Sydney</GPE>. While there, <PERSON>Christian</PERSON> encounters <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> in a bar and tells him that he wanted to apologize and tell his son that he did the right thing, but is too weak to call him. <PERSON>Christian Shephard</PERSON> later dies of a massive heart attack brought on by alcohol poisoning. When|<PERSON>Jack</PERSON> leaves <GPE>the United States</GPE>, he knows only that his father is missing.|Eventually he finds him in a <GPE>Sydney</GPE> morgue. <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> has", "global_chunk_number": 8, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["Jack", "leaves", "the", "United", "States", "he", "knows"], "start_time": 217680, "end_time": 220220, "start_index": 547, "end_index": 554}, "mid": {"tokens": ["Eventually", "he", "finds", "him", "in", "a", "Sydney", "morgue", "Jack", "has", "trouble", "getting", "the", "casket", "onto", "the", "plane"], "start_time": 222410, "end_time": 228160, "start_index": 560, "end_index": 577}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "<PERSON>Jack</PERSON> leaves <GPE>the United States</GPE>, he knows only that his father is missing. Eventually he finds him in a <GPE>Sydney</GPE> morgue. <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> has trouble getting the casket onto the plane", "segmented_puncted_text": "<PERSON>Jack</PERSON> leaves <GPE>the United States</GPE>, he knows only that his father is missing.|Eventually he finds him in a <GPE>Sydney</GPE> morgue. <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> has trouble getting the casket onto the plane |", "global_chunk_number": 9, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["she", "was", "Christian's", "bodyguard", "and", "drinking", "buddy", "while", "in", "Australia", "On", "the", "plane", "he", "is", "seated", "next", "to", "Rose", "When", "the", "turbulence", "strikes", "Rose's", "husband", "is", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "start_time": 248600, "end_time": 259480, "start_index": 633, "end_index": 662}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "she was Christian's bodyguard and drinking buddy while in <GPE>Australia</GPE>. On the plane, he is seated next to <PERSON>Rose</PERSON>. When the turbulence strikes, Rose's husband is in the bathroom", "segmented_puncted_text": "|she was Christian's bodyguard and drinking buddy while in <GPE>Australia</GPE>. On the plane, he is seated next to <PERSON>Rose</PERSON>. When the turbulence strikes, Rose's husband is in the bathroom |", "global_chunk_number": 10, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["When", "the", "turbulence", "strikes", "Rose's", "husband", "is", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "start_time": 255580, "end_time": 259480, "start_index": 652, "end_index": 662}, "mid": {"tokens": ["seat", "number", "during", "the", "flight", "is", "twenty", "three", "B", "it", "should", "be", "noted", "that", "this", "is", "one", "of", "the", "numbers", "Jack's", "wedding", "date", "was", "August", "fifteenth", "or", "eight", "forward", "slash", "fifteen", "the", "same"], "start_time": 269100, "end_time": 280060, "start_index": 684, "end_index": 717}, "right": {"tokens": ["number", "as", "the", "doomed", "flight"], "start_time": 280060, "end_time": 281450, "start_index": 717, "end_index": 722}, "puncted_text": "When the turbulence strikes, Rose's husband is in the bathroom and <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> promises to take care of her until he returns. Before the plane's tail section broke off, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> loses consciousness. Jack's seat number during the flight is <NUMERIC>23</NUMERIC> B; it should be noted that this is one of the numbers. Jack's wedding date was <DATE>August 15th</DATE>, or <DATE>8/15</DATE>, the same number as the doomed flight,", "segmented_puncted_text": "When the turbulence strikes, Rose's husband is in the bathroom and <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> promises to take care of her until he returns. Before the plane's tail section broke off, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> loses consciousness. Jack's|seat number during the flight is <NUMERIC>23</NUMERIC> B; it should be noted that this is one of the numbers. Jack's wedding date was <DATE>August 15th</DATE>, or <DATE>8/15</DATE>, the same|number as the doomed flight,", "global_chunk_number": 11, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["date", "was", "August", "fifteenth", "or", "eight", "forward", "slash", "fifteen", "the", "same"], "start_time": 276080, "end_time": 280060, "start_index": 706, "end_index": 717}, "mid": {"tokens": ["number", "as", "the", "doomed", "flight", "and", "also", "the", "same", "as", "two", "of", "the", "numbers", "At", "the", "beginning", "of", "Pilot", "Part", "one", "we", "see", "that", "Jack", "was", "thrown", "into", "the", "woods", "and", "had", "multiple", "gashes", "including", "a", "large"], "start_time": 280060, "end_time": 295980, "start_index": 717, "end_index": 754}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "date was <DATE>August 15th</DATE>, or <DATE>8/15</DATE>, the same number as the doomed flight, and also the same as <CARDINAL>two</CARDINAL> of the numbers. At the beginning of \" <WORK_OF_ART>Pilot: Part 1 \"</WORK_OF_ART>, we see that <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> was thrown into the woods and had multiple gashes, including a large", "segmented_puncted_text": "date was <DATE>August 15th</DATE>, or <DATE>8/15</DATE>, the same|number as the doomed flight, and also the same as <CARDINAL>two</CARDINAL> of the numbers. At the beginning of \" <WORK_OF_ART>Pilot: Part 1 \"</WORK_OF_ART>, we see that <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> was thrown into the woods and had multiple gashes, including a large |", "global_chunk_number": 12, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["including", "a", "large"], "start_time": 295130, "end_time": 295980, "start_index": 751, "end_index": 754}, "mid": {"tokens": ["back", "marking", "the", "beginning", "of", "their", "friendship", "He", "leads", "an", "expedition", "with", "Kate", "and", "Charlie", "to", "find", "the", "cockpit", "and", "the", "plane's", "transceiver", "Together", "they", "find", "it", "but", "also", "witness", "the", "pilot's", "death", "at", "the", "hands", "of", "the", "monster"], "start_time": 306590, "end_time": 320170, "start_index": 788, "end_index": 827}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "including a large one on his back. Upon finding the plane's wreckage on the beach, he tends to many survivors but is unable to save all of them. He enlists <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> to sew the gash on his back, marking the beginning of their friendship. He leads an expedition with <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> and <PERSON>Charlie</PERSON> to find the cockpit and the plane's transceiver. Together they find it but also witness the pilot's death at the hands of the \" monster \".", "segmented_puncted_text": "including a large one on his back. Upon finding the plane's wreckage on the beach, he tends to many survivors but is unable to save all of them. He enlists <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> to sew the gash on his|back, marking the beginning of their friendship. He leads an expedition with <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> and <PERSON>Charlie</PERSON> to find the cockpit and the plane's transceiver. Together they find it but also witness the pilot's death at the hands of the \" monster \". |", "global_chunk_number": 13, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["also", "witness", "the", "pilot's", "death", "at", "the", "hands", "of", "the", "monster"], "start_time": 317080, "end_time": 320170, "start_index": 816, "end_index": 827}, "mid": {"tokens": ["Jack", "is", "quickly", "thrust", "into", "a", "leadership", "role", "by", "the", "other", "survivors", "because", "of", "his", "medical", "training", "and", "take", "charge", "attitude", "He", "quickly", "develops", "a", "rivalry", "with", "Sawyer", "mainly"], "start_time": 326170, "end_time": 336170, "start_index": 827, "end_index": 856}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "also witness the pilot's death at the hands of the \" monster \". <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> is quickly thrust into a leadership role by the other survivors because of his medical training and take-charge attitude. He quickly develops a rivalry with <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON>, mainly", "segmented_puncted_text": "also witness the pilot's death at the hands of the \" monster \".|<PERSON>Jack</PERSON> is quickly thrust into a leadership role by the other survivors because of his medical training and take-charge attitude. He quickly develops a rivalry with <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON>, mainly |", "global_chunk_number": 14, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["suffered", "fatal", "injuries", "in", "the", "previous", "episode", "However", "he", "finds", "himself", "still", "having", "trouble", "letting", "go"], "start_time": 422600, "end_time": 430280, "start_index": 1093, "end_index": 1109}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "suffered fatal injuries in the previous episode. However, he finds himself still having trouble letting go,", "segmented_puncted_text": "|suffered fatal injuries in the previous episode. However, he finds himself still having trouble letting go, |", "global_chunk_number": 15, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["to", "Locke", "not", "telling", "Jack", "everything", "that's", "going", "on", "In", "Exodus", "Jack", "is", "part", "of", "the", "team", "that", "retrieves", "the", "dynamite", "at", "the"], "start_time": 452370, "end_time": 460050, "start_index": 1159, "end_index": 1182}, "right": {"tokens": ["Black", "Rock", "and", "that", "plans", "to", "open", "the", "mysterious", "hatch", "Before", "he", "leaves"], "start_time": 460050, "end_time": 465450, "start_index": 1182, "end_index": 1195}, "puncted_text": "to <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> not telling <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> everything that's going on. In \" <WORK_OF_ART>Exodus</WORK_OF_ART> \", <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> is part of the team that retrieves the dynamite at <FAC>the \" Black Rock \"</FAC> and that plans to open the mysterious hatch. Before he leaves,", "segmented_puncted_text": "|to <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> not telling <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> everything that's going on. In \" <WORK_OF_ART>Exodus</WORK_OF_ART> \", <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> is part of the team that retrieves the dynamite at <FAC>the \"|Black Rock \"</FAC> and that plans to open the mysterious hatch. Before he leaves,", "global_chunk_number": 16, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["dynamite", "at", "the"], "start_time": 459340, "end_time": 460050, "start_index": 1179, "end_index": 1182}, "mid": {"tokens": ["Black", "Rock", "and", "that", "plans", "to", "open", "the", "mysterious", "hatch", "Before", "he", "leaves", "he"], "start_time": 460050, "end_time": 465890, "start_index": 1182, "end_index": 1196}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "dynamite at <FAC>the \" Black Rock \"</FAC> and that plans to open the mysterious hatch. Before he leaves, he", "segmented_puncted_text": "dynamite at <FAC>the \"|Black Rock \"</FAC> and that plans to open the mysterious hatch. Before he leaves, he |", "global_chunk_number": 17, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["descends", "into", "the", "hatch", "after", "Kate", "and", "Locke", "He", "explores", "the", "rooms", "underground", "and", "is", "surprised", "by"], "start_time": 485770, "end_time": 493120, "start_index": 1262, "end_index": 1279}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "descends into the hatch after <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> and <PERSON>Locke</PERSON>. He explores the rooms underground and is surprised by", "segmented_puncted_text": "|descends into the hatch after <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> and <PERSON>Locke</PERSON>. He explores the rooms underground and is surprised by |", "global_chunk_number": 18, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["she", "accidentally", "shot", "and", "killed", "fellow", "castaway", "Shannon", "Rutherford", "In", "What", "Kate", "Did", "Jack", "struggles", "with", "his", "unresolved", "feelings", "for", "Kate", "The"], "start_time": 510510, "end_time": 519340, "start_index": 1333, "end_index": 1355}, "right": {"tokens": ["situation", "is", "complicated", "when", "an", "injured", "and", "delirious", "Sawyer", "declares"], "start_time": 520340, "end_time": 524850, "start_index": 1355, "end_index": 1365}, "puncted_text": "she accidentally shot and killed fellow castaway <PERSON>Shannon Rutherford</PERSON>. In <WORK_OF_ART>\" What Kate Did \"</WORK_OF_ART> <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> struggles with his unresolved feelings for <PERSON>Kate</PERSON>. The situation is complicated when an injured and delirious <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> declares", "segmented_puncted_text": "|she accidentally shot and killed fellow castaway <PERSON>Shannon Rutherford</PERSON>. In <WORK_OF_ART>\" What Kate Did \"</WORK_OF_ART> <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> struggles with his unresolved feelings for <PERSON>Kate</PERSON>. The|situation is complicated when an injured and delirious <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> declares", "global_chunk_number": 19, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["What", "Kate", "Did", "Jack", "struggles", "with", "his", "unresolved", "feelings", "for", "Kate", "The"], "start_time": 515430, "end_time": 519340, "start_index": 1343, "end_index": 1355}, "mid": {"tokens": ["situation", "is", "complicated", "when", "an", "injured", "and", "delirious", "Sawyer", "declares"], "start_time": 520340, "end_time": 524850, "start_index": 1355, "end_index": 1365}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "What Kate Did \"</WORK_OF_ART> <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> struggles with his unresolved feelings for <PERSON>Kate</PERSON>. The situation is complicated when an injured and delirious <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> declares", "segmented_puncted_text": "What Kate Did \"</WORK_OF_ART> <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> struggles with his unresolved feelings for <PERSON>Kate</PERSON>. The|situation is complicated when an injured and delirious <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> declares |", "global_chunk_number": 20, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["follows", "them", "anyway", "and", "is", "taken", "hostage", "by", "mister", "Friendly"], "start_time": 554140, "end_time": 557940, "start_index": 1457, "end_index": 1467}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "follows them anyway, and is taken hostage by Mr. <PERSON>Friendly</PERSON>.", "segmented_puncted_text": "|follows them anyway, and is taken hostage by Mr. <PERSON>Friendly</PERSON>. |", "global_chunk_number": 21, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["and", "is", "taken", "hostage", "by", "mister", "Friendly"], "start_time": 555740, "end_time": 557940, "start_index": 1460, "end_index": 1467}, "mid": {"tokens": ["how", "long", "she", "thinks", "it", "would", "take", "to", "train", "an", "army", "In", "The", "Long", "Con", "after", "Locke", "moves", "the", "guns", "they", "argue", "about", "the", "state", "of", "their", "trust", "in", "each", "other", "In", "One", "of", "Them", "as", "the", "interrogation"], "start_time": 568620, "end_time": 581230, "start_index": 1489, "end_index": 1527}, "right": {"tokens": ["in", "the", "armory", "get", "out", "of", "control", "Jack", "holds", "Locke", "against", "the", "wall"], "start_time": 581230, "end_time": 585310, "start_index": 1527, "end_index": 1540}, "puncted_text": "and is taken hostage by Mr. <PERSON>Friendly</PERSON>. After a brief standoff, the flight survivors drop their weapons, and <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> apologizes for following the group. Later, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> asks <PERSON>Ana Lucia</PERSON> how long she thinks it would take to \" train an army. \" In <WORK_OF_ART>\" The Long Con \"</WORK_OF_ART>, after <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> moves the guns they argue about the state of their trust in each other. In \" <CARDINAL>One</CARDINAL> of Them \", as the interrogation in the armory get out of control, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> holds <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> against the wall", "segmented_puncted_text": "and is taken hostage by Mr. <PERSON>Friendly</PERSON>. After a brief standoff, the flight survivors drop their weapons, and <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> apologizes for following the group. Later, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> asks <PERSON>Ana Lucia</PERSON>|how long she thinks it would take to \" train an army. \" In <WORK_OF_ART>\" The Long Con \"</WORK_OF_ART>, after <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> moves the guns they argue about the state of their trust in each other. In \" <CARDINAL>One</CARDINAL> of Them \", as the interrogation|in the armory get out of control, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> holds <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> against the wall", "global_chunk_number": 22, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["argue", "about", "the", "state", "of", "their", "trust", "in", "each", "other", "In", "One", "of", "Them", "as", "the", "interrogation"], "start_time": 575560, "end_time": 581230, "start_index": 1510, "end_index": 1527}, "mid": {"tokens": ["in", "the", "armory", "get", "out", "of", "control", "Jack", "holds", "Locke", "against", "the", "wall", "and", "demands", "him", "to", "unlock", "the", "armory", "The", "timer", "goes", "off", "and", "with", "few", "seconds", "to", "spare", "Locke", "complies", "with", "Jack", "and", "lets", "him", "in", "to", "stop", "the", "interrogation", "In", "Lockdown", "Jack", "takes", "care", "of", "Aaron", "who", "is", "running", "a", "fever"], "start_time": 581230, "end_time": 600020, "start_index": 1527, "end_index": 1581}, "right": {"tokens": ["and", "is", "approached", "by", "Libby", "who", "was", "stung", "by", "a", "sea", "urchin", "He", "comments", "to", "Libby"], "start_time": 600410, "end_time": 605130, "start_index": 1581, "end_index": 1597}, "puncted_text": "argue about the state of their trust in each other. In \" <CARDINAL>One</CARDINAL> of Them \", as the interrogation in the armory get out of control, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> holds <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> against the wall and demands him to unlock the armory. The timer goes off and with <TIME>few seconds</TIME> to spare, <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> complies with <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> and lets him in to stop the interrogation. In \" <WORK_OF_ART>Lockdown</WORK_OF_ART> \", <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> takes care of <PERSON>Aaron</PERSON>, who is running a fever, and is approached by <PERSON>Libby</PERSON>, who was stung by a sea urchin. He comments to <PERSON>Libby</PERSON>", "segmented_puncted_text": "argue about the state of their trust in each other. In \" <CARDINAL>One</CARDINAL> of Them \", as the interrogation|in the armory get out of control, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> holds <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> against the wall and demands him to unlock the armory. The timer goes off and with <TIME>few seconds</TIME> to spare, <PERSON>Locke</PERSON> complies with <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> and lets him in to stop the interrogation. In \" <WORK_OF_ART>Lockdown</WORK_OF_ART> \", <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> takes care of <PERSON>Aaron</PERSON>, who is running a fever,|and is approached by <PERSON>Libby</PERSON>, who was stung by a sea urchin. He comments to <PERSON>Libby</PERSON>", "global_chunk_number": 23, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["Lockdown", "Jack", "takes", "care", "of", "Aaron", "who", "is", "running", "a", "fever"], "start_time": 596240, "end_time": 600020, "start_index": 1570, "end_index": 1581}, "mid": {"tokens": ["and", "is", "approached", "by", "Libby", "who", "was", "stung", "by", "a", "sea", "urchin", "He", "comments", "to", "Libby", "that", "some", "Neosporin", "should", "help", "to", "which", "she", "replies", "that", "the", "going", "rate", "of", "exchange", "for", "Neosporin", "is", "ten", "loads", "of", "laundry", "alluding", "to", "Sawyer", "who", "stole", "all", "the", "medical", "supplies", "from", "the", "hatch", "Sawyer", "is", "playing", "poker", "with", "Hurley", "and", "Kate", "for", "mangoes"], "start_time": 600410, "end_time": 620310, "start_index": 1581, "end_index": 1641}, "right": {"tokens": ["shows", "some", "knowledge", "of", "poker", "when", "he", "advises"], "start_time": 621320, "end_time": 623820, "start_index": 1642, "end_index": 1650}, "puncted_text": "<WORK_OF_ART>Lockdown</WORK_OF_ART> \", <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> takes care of <PERSON>Aaron</PERSON>, who is running a fever, and is approached by <PERSON>Libby</PERSON>, who was stung by a sea urchin. He comments to <PERSON>Libby</PERSON> that some Neosporin should help, to which she replies that the going rate of exchange for <PRODUCT>Neosporin</PRODUCT> is <QUANTITY>10</QUANTITY> loads of laundry, alluding to <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON>, who stole all the medical supplies from the hatch. <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> is playing poker with <PERSON>Hurley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> for mangoes. Jack shows some knowledge of poker when he advises", "segmented_puncted_text": "<WORK_OF_ART>Lockdown</WORK_OF_ART> \", <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> takes care of <PERSON>Aaron</PERSON>, who is running a fever,|and is approached by <PERSON>Libby</PERSON>, who was stung by a sea urchin. He comments to <PERSON>Libby</PERSON> that some Neosporin should help, to which she replies that the going rate of exchange for <PRODUCT>Neosporin</PRODUCT> is <QUANTITY>10</QUANTITY> loads of laundry, alluding to <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON>, who stole all the medical supplies from the hatch. <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> is playing poker with <PERSON>Hurley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> for mangoes. Jack|shows some knowledge of poker when he advises", "global_chunk_number": 24, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["supplies", "from", "the", "hatch", "Sawyer", "is", "playing", "poker", "with", "Hurley", "and", "Kate", "for", "mangoes"], "start_time": 615090, "end_time": 620310, "start_index": 1627, "end_index": 1641}, "mid": {"tokens": ["shows", "some", "knowledge", "of", "poker", "when", "he", "advises"], "start_time": 621320, "end_time": 623820, "start_index": 1642, "end_index": 1650}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "supplies from the hatch. <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> is playing poker with <PERSON>Hurley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> for mangoes. Jack shows some knowledge of poker when he advises", "segmented_puncted_text": "supplies from the hatch. <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> is playing poker with <PERSON>Hurley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Kate</PERSON> for mangoes. Jack|shows some knowledge of poker when he advises |", "global_chunk_number": 25, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["to", "leave", "Sawyer", "raises", "the", "stakes", "offering"], "start_time": 651130, "end_time": 654670, "start_index": 1730, "end_index": 1737}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "to leave, <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> raises the stakes, offering", "segmented_puncted_text": "|to leave, <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> raises the stakes, offering |", "global_chunk_number": 26, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["Immediately", "the", "sound", "of", "a", "twig", "snapping"], "start_time": 750440, "end_time": 752750, "start_index": 2009, "end_index": 2016}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "Immediately, the sound of a twig snapping", "segmented_puncted_text": "|Immediately, the sound of a twig snapping |", "global_chunk_number": 27, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["visible", "as", "they", "begin", "talking", "a", "little", "more", "Sawyer", "asks", "Jack", "about", "his", "trek", "into", "the", "jungle"], "start_time": 815080, "end_time": 820440, "start_index": 2188, "end_index": 2205}, "right": {"tokens": ["with", "Kate", "to"], "start_time": 820440, "end_time": 821860, "start_index": 2205, "end_index": 2208}, "puncted_text": "visible as they begin talking a little more. <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> asks <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> about his trek into the jungle with <PERSON>Kate</PERSON>, to", "segmented_puncted_text": "|visible as they begin talking a little more. <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> asks <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> about his trek into the jungle|with <PERSON>Kate</PERSON>, to", "global_chunk_number": 28, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["visible", "as", "they", "begin", "talking", "a", "little", "more", "Sawyer", "asks", "Jack", "about", "his", "trek", "into", "the", "jungle"], "start_time": 815080, "end_time": 820440, "start_index": 2188, "end_index": 2205}, "mid": {"tokens": ["with", "Kate", "to"], "start_time": 820440, "end_time": 821860, "start_index": 2205, "end_index": 2208}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "visible as they begin talking a little more. <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> asks <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> about his trek into the jungle with <PERSON>Kate</PERSON>, to", "segmented_puncted_text": "visible as they begin talking a little more. <PERSON>Sawyer</PERSON> asks <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> about his trek into the jungle|with <PERSON>Kate</PERSON>, to |", "global_chunk_number": 29, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["work", "In", "Live", "Together", "Die", "Alone", "Sayid"], "start_time": 850960, "end_time": 855470, "start_index": 2297, "end_index": 2304}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "work. \" In <WORK_OF_ART>\" Live Together, Die Alone \"</WORK_OF_ART>, <PERSON>Sayid</PERSON>", "segmented_puncted_text": "|work. \" In <WORK_OF_ART>\" Live Together, Die Alone \"</WORK_OF_ART>, <PERSON>Sayid</PERSON> |", "global_chunk_number": 30, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "mid": {"tokens": ["island", "with", "Walt", "via", "boat", "Hurley", "is", "let", "go", "The", "fate", "of", "the", "three", "is", "unknown", "although", "Henry", "Gale", "states", "that", "they", "will", "not", "be", "harmed", "and", "that", "they", "will", "live", "with"], "start_time": 890190, "end_time": 900010, "start_index": 2409, "end_index": 2441}, "right": {"tokens": ["the", "Others", "In", "the"], "start_time": 900010, "end_time": 902680, "start_index": 2441, "end_index": 2445}, "puncted_text": "island with <PERSON>Walt</PERSON> via boat. <PERSON>Hurley</PERSON> is let go. The fate of the <CARDINAL>three</CARDINAL> is unknown, although <PERSON>\" Henry Gale \"</PERSON> states that they will not be harmed and that they will live with the Others. In the", "segmented_puncted_text": "|island with <PERSON>Walt</PERSON> via boat. <PERSON>Hurley</PERSON> is let go. The fate of the <CARDINAL>three</CARDINAL> is unknown, although <PERSON>\" Henry Gale \"</PERSON> states that they will not be harmed and that they will live with|the Others. In the", "global_chunk_number": 31, "filename": "aligned.swc"}, {"left": {"tokens": ["is", "unknown", "although", "Henry", "Gale", "states", "that", "they", "will", "not", "be", "harmed", "and", "that", "they", "will", "live", "with"], "start_time": 895250, "end_time": 900010, "start_index": 2423, "end_index": 2441}, "mid": {"tokens": ["the", "Others", "In", "the", "original", "outline", "of", "the", "pilot", "episode", "Jack", "was", "supposed", "to", "be", "killed", "halfway", "through", "the", "two", "part", "pilot", "however", "early", "readers", "claimed", "killing", "him"], "start_time": 900010, "end_time": 914050, "start_index": 2441, "end_index": 2469}, "right": {"tokens": [], "start_time": null, "end_time": null, "start_index": null, "end_index": null}, "puncted_text": "is unknown, although <PERSON>\" Henry Gale \"</PERSON> states that they will not be harmed and that they will live with the Others. In the original outline of the pilot episode, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> was supposed to be killed halfway through the two-part pilot; however, early readers claimed killing him", "segmented_puncted_text": "is unknown, although <PERSON>\" Henry Gale \"</PERSON> states that they will not be harmed and that they will live with|the Others. In the original outline of the pilot episode, <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> was supposed to be killed halfway through the two-part pilot; however, early readers claimed killing him |", "global_chunk_number": 32, "filename": "aligned.swc"}]}

